Sadie Mothershed

Atlanta, GA 30306 | 404-263-8899 | smothershed3@gatech.edu | U.S. Citizen https://saxvi.github.io/port/index.html

Objective

Third-year Computational Media student seeking a UX/UI, visual design, or product design internship opportunity for Summer or Fal 2023. Looking to apply 4 years of interpersonal communication experience in a collaborative environment that encourages hands-on work.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA

June 2020 – Present

Bachelor of Science in Computational Media, 3.16

Expected Graduation May 2024

Skills

Programming: Python, Java, HTML5, CSS, basic Javascript

Platforms: Windows, MacOS, Linux

Software: Adobe InDesign, Illustrator, Blender, Fusion360, Office365

Communication: Design proposals, written informational reports, project presentations

Languages: English, intermediate French

Experience

ACE Volleyball and Athletics | Atlanta, GA

October 2019 - Present

Volleyball Coach

- Leading practices and running drills with players, coaching teams of 9-20 elementary to high school aged girls, instructing on specific skills, techniques, and strategies to allow players to accomplish their goals
- Acting as liaison between parents and club coordinator, facilitating open conversation and employing effective problem-solving strategies

Georgia Tech Alumni Association Magazine | Atlanta, GA

October 2022 – Present

Student Assistant

- Researching facts and details of new features to ensure correctness
- Reviewing written work for accuracy, content, sense, and cohesiveness and providing suggestions for improvements
- Managing, updating, and formatting Alumni News website with new entries using HTML

Georgia Tech IT, Wreck Techs | Atlanta, GA

August – December 2021

Resident Technical Assistant

- Assisting 5-20 customers per 4-hour shift with technical issues via phone, email, and in-person communication
- Connecting and troubleshooting devices on the wired and wireless campus networks
- Repairing and configuring software-related issues on Windows and Mac operating systems

Relevant Coursework

Intro Computational Media: Completed various projects centered around user interface design, web design, and app-building, including building my online portfolio, designing a Twitter Bot, and creating a rudimentary game with JavaScript.

Objects and Design: Studied and executed various object-oriented methods for dealing with large programs, including quality processes, debugging techniques, and testing. Designed and coded a Pacman game with a group over the course of a semester.

Data Structures and Algorithms: Studied computer data structures and algorithms in the context of object-oriented programming with a focus on software development towards applications.